<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.getpostman.Postman</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Postman</name>
  <summary>Postman is a complete API development environment.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Postman is the complete toolchain for API developers, used by 5 million
      developers and more than 100,000 companies worldwide to access 130 million
      APIs every month. Postman makes working with APIs faster and easier by
      supporting developers at every stage of their workflow, and is available
      for macOS, Windows, Linux and Chrome users.
    </p>
    <p>
      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by
      Postman or Postdot Technologies.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.getpostman.com/img/pages/products/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.getpostman.com</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.18.0" date="2020-02-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Visualizer is now out of beta!</li>
          <li>GraphQL is now out of beta!</li>
          <li>Added ability for users to request higher roles on APIs shared within a team.</li>
          <li>Added confirmation for unsaved changes on accidentally closing the modal during mock creation flow.</li>
          <li>Disabled JSON language option for RAML type schemas.</li>
          <li>Renaming a request re-opened all items in Collections tab of sidebar when a filter was set [#6624].</li>
          <li>Script pane was crashing when accessing a collection variable with object value [#7759].</li>
          <li>Double borders for request URL were shown when zooming in or out [#5230].</li>
          <li>Blank page appeared while creating a mock server [#7751].</li>
          <li>Cookies with Max-Age were not deleted.</li>
          <li>data-file with BOM characters or encoding other than UTF-8 were not working.</li>
          <li>API tab was getting stuck in the loading state when the user is offline.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
