<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.getpostman.Postman</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Postman</name>
  <summary>Postman is a complete API development environment.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Postman is the complete toolchain for API developers, used by 5 million
      developers and more than 100,000 companies worldwide to access 130 million
      APIs every month. Postman makes working with APIs faster and easier by
      supporting developers at every stage of their workflow, and is available
      for macOS, Windows, Linux and Chrome users.
    </p>
    <p>
      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by
      Postman or Postdot Technologies.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.getpostman.com/img/pages/products/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.getpostman.com</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.20.0" date="2020-03-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>UI changes for comments in app</li>
          <li>Show a warning when accessing cookies using script for a domain that is not whitelisted</li>
          <li>Improvements in import folder flow</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5752] - Updated URL encoding behavior as per WHATWG URL standard</li>
          <li>Updated the Create New API flow in the API builder</li>
          <li>Create linking between mock listing and call logs view</li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where variables with reserved characters (`#`, `?`, `:`, etc.) in URL were not being resolved</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7848] - Fixed a bug where an object as variable key crashes the script editor</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6852] - Fixed an issue where default value for 'Automatically persist variable values' setting was set to true.</li>
          <li>[GitHub #2366] - Disable automatic addition of content-type headers when selecting language</li>
          <li>Fixed the placeholder text for collection and folder descriptions</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
