<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.getpostman.Postman</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Postman</name>
  <summary>Postman is a complete API development environment.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Postman is the complete toolchain for API developers, used by 5 million
      developers and more than 100,000 companies worldwide to access 130 million
      APIs every month. Postman makes working with APIs faster and easier by
      supporting developers at every stage of their workflow, and is available
      for macOS, Windows, Linux and Chrome users.
    </p>
    <p>
      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by
      Postman or Postdot Technologies.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.getpostman.com/img/pages/products/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.getpostman.com</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.19.1" date="2020-02-25">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>[GitHub #7433] - Monospace editor font not loading in Linux</li>
          <li>Fixed an issue where response was rendered in light theme even when dark theme was selected.</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7745] - Fixed issue where undo did not work while naming/renaming a request in a tab</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7823] - Fixed an issue where double clicking on title bar in maximised state makes window invisible</li>
          <li>Disable minute timer for free user on monitor creation</li>
          <li>Fixed an issue where placement of "Beautify" button in request body in two pane layout was inconsistent with single pane layout</li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where request editor tabs would overlap in two pane layout when resizing</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7997] - Fixed a bug in Runner where result items of a run overlapped on retrying a run.</li>
          <li>Create new monitors when in Browse mode, even if monitors already exist.</li>
          <li>Add entry point in collection drop-down menu for pull request.</li>
          <li>List all roles available on Postman entities in accordance to team plan</li>
          <li>Added "Request Access" button in error toasts when user lacks permission while editing schema or API version</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
