<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.getpostman.Postman</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Postman</name>
  <summary>Postman is a complete API development environment.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Postman is the complete toolchain for API developers, used by 5 million
      developers and more than 100,000 companies worldwide to access 130 million
      APIs every month. Postman makes working with APIs faster and easier by
      supporting developers at every stage of their workflow, and is available
      for macOS, Windows, Linux and Chrome users.
    </p>
    <p>
      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by
      Postman or Postdot Technologies.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.getpostman.com/img/pages/products/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.getpostman.com</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.6.0" date="2019-08-29">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>[GitHub #7032] - Fixed an issue where OAuth2 was not working for callback URLs with custom protocol</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6989] - Fixed an issue where labels in Tab Actions dropdown were breaking due to longer shortcuts on Windows</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6805] - Changed Licences to Licenses in About tab of Settings modal</li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where wrong error message is displayed while generating link for inviting users.</li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where on opening environments from browse view used to lead to a broken link.</li>
          <li>Disabled all actions on workspaces in runner's workspace switcher.</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6980] - Fixed an issue causing scroll issues when having multiple iteration in Runner Results</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5251] - Fixed issue in Manage cookies modal where delete domain action collapses the domain accordion</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5762] - Suppress bad string error for variables in JSON Example response</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5711] - Fixed a bug where browse mode shows no environments for workspace, after duplicating an environment</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5259] - Fixed a bug in console where only the last value of params with same keys was logged</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6783] - Fix a bug where errors were not shown in console for raw mode</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6662] - Fixed a bug where form data file reference was lost after saving a request to collection</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6868] - Fixed a bug where GraphQL request was getting stuck with AWS and Hawk authentication</li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where runner data import preview was not showing false boolean values</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6923] - Fixed a bug where image was not detected in response body</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7008] - Fixed a bug where runner would not recognize extensions for data files</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6110] - Fixed the export issue in Collection Runner</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6837] - Fixed a bug where object was shown as [object Object] in runner file preview</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6961] - Added a deleted state for Runner when a collection is modified</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6463] - Stopped syncing and saving of large examples (above 5Mb)</li>
          <li>Update messaging around working-directory setting</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6765] - Modified behaviour of $randomPhoneNumber and added $randomPhoneNumberExt</li>
          <li>[GitHub #2922] - Added support for variable substitution using `replaceIn` method</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6641] - Added HTTP version in raw mode console logs for requests</li>
          <li>Added info button in response headers UI explaining purpose of each header</li>
          <li>[GitHub #3525] - Add variable resolution in OAuth2 authorization token name</li>
          <li>Added Multi Select and Bulk Actions in Runner</li>
          <li>Added ESC key shortcut to close right overlay modal in API tab</li>
          <li>[GitHub #4133] - Added C, PHP pecl_http, Python http.client, Httpie modes to the experimental codegen feature</li>
          <li>[GitHub #2638] - Modified resolution of all *.localhost addresses to 127.0.0.1</li>
          <li>[GitHub #3312] - Added support for programmatic cookie access via scripts</li>
          <li>Create mock-server/monitor and add to the API in API tab</li>
          <li>Add collection to the API as documentation or test while generating collection from schema</li>
          <li>Add collection to the API as documentation or test while adding version tag from collection changelog</li>
          <li>Realtime Collaboration in API Dev Platform</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
