<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.getpostman.Postman</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Postman</name>
  <summary>Postman is a complete API development environment.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Postman is the complete toolchain for API developers, used by 5 million
      developers and more than 100,000 companies worldwide to access 130 million
      APIs every month. Postman makes working with APIs faster and easier by
      supporting developers at every stage of their workflow, and is available
      for macOS, Windows, Linux and Chrome users.
    </p>
    <p>
      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by
      Postman or Postdot Technologies.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.getpostman.com/img/pages/products/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.getpostman.com</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.10.0" date="2019-10-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>[GitHub #6449] - Added the settings -> update tab back in Postman Snap app</li>
          <li>[GitHub #3835] - Added warnings to request-header editor when invalid characters are identified</li>
          <li>Update the Postman Console to new user interface</li>
          <li>Disable XML from dropdown when openapi 1/2/3 selected as type</li>
          <li>Show API name in collection browser</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7299] - Fixed an issue where runner was using disabled collection variables while running a collection</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7288] - Fixed a bug where cookies were not updated in Collection Runner</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7437] - Fixed an issue where `Beautify` button was not visible when language was inferred from Content-Type header</li>
          <li>[GitHub #7051] - Fixed an issue where HttpOnly cookie was not getting updated to non-HttpOnly</li>
          <li>Disallow creation of version tags on collections for free users on the non-latest state of a collection</li>
          <li>Fixed an issue where example request was missing after resolving conflicts</li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where app used to stay in build mode on workspace leave action</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6966] - Added support for Akamai EdgeGrid authentication</li>
          <li>Schema changelog</li>
          <li>Added flow to allow creating APIs by importing schema</li>
          <li>Added support to redirect relations to dashboard</li>
          <li>Ability to create APIs from CNX flow</li>
          <li>Improved UI and extended functionality of API Network in the app</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
