<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.getpostman.Postman</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Postman</name>
  <summary>Postman is a complete API development environment.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Postman is the complete toolchain for API developers, used by 5 million
      developers and more than 100,000 companies worldwide to access 130 million
      APIs every month. Postman makes working with APIs faster and easier by
      supporting developers at every stage of their workflow, and is available
      for macOS, Windows, Linux and Chrome users.

      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by
      Postman or Postdot Technologies.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.getpostman.com/img/pages/products/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.getpostman.com</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.3.5" date="2019-07-31">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>[GitHub #7001] - Fixed an issue where SSO login was not working for Enterprise login</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.3.4" date="2019-07-19">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Discontinue support for 32-bit Linux</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6595] - Improved pm.variables.has method to search in all the scopes</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6699] - Updated response viewer to show headers in a tabular view</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6414] - Updated request headers to be title case for consistency</li>
          <li>Updated response-viewer to show different stages of request accurately</li>
          <li>This release replaces the rich editor used for displaying the response from Ace Editor to Monaco editor</li>
          <li>In addition to changing the editor for the response section, the pretty view no longer does transformations on the response text. All transformations are handled as text formatters inside the editor</li>
          <li>Combined, these two above changes give better performance, reduced memory footprint and remove bugs in response pretty view</li>
          <li>[GitHub #4721] - Fixed an issue where app crashed on de-structured usage of pm assertions</li>
          <li>[GitHub #4591] - Fixed an issue where collection runner was not identifying JSON format when selecting data file</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5381] - Fixed an issue where export collection dialogue breaks on expanding (macOS)</li>
          <li>[GitHub #4412] - Fixed an issue where loader window was not appearing centered on using multiple monitors on Linux</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6784] - Fixed a bug where parsing CSV file containing double quotes as escape character caused error</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6752] - Fix a bug causing app to crash when form-data has malformed file value</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6140] - Fixed a bug where multipart/form-data boundary was inconsistent for digest auth</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6651] - Fixed a bug where pm.sendRequest crashes the app for the non-string raw body</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6761] - Fixed a bug causing non utf8 charset responses to not show in the response-viewer</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6764] - Fixed a bug where using quotes inside unquoted csv field caused error</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6730] - Fixed a bug where collection export was not working when example request was empty</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6754] - Fixed a bug where undo history was reset after performing a beautify action</li>
          <li>[GitHub #1465] - Fixed a bug where floating point numbers were rounded off in response pretty view</li>
          <li>[GitHub #5712] - Fixed a bug where JSON response pretty view removed extra characters surrounding the JSON text</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6150] - Fixed a bug where emoji in response viewer caused uneven line heights</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6103] - Fixed a bug where search pop-up would hide the scrollbar in response pretty view</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6807] - Fixed a bug where cookies were not stored when the cookie path did not match the request path</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6767] - Fixed an issue where collection sidebar history items did not have pointer cursor on hover</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6860] - Fixed a bug where links in response viewer were encoded when opened in a Tab</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6891] - Fixed a bug in Examples causing editor to beautify on every key-stroke</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6932] - Fixed an issue where app was opening only once by clicking on "Run in Postman" button and not launching again.</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6886] - Fixed an issue where requests sent to servers that use TLS renegotiation were not working</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6895] - Fixed issue where OAuth2 window was showing blank screen on requesting token</li>
          <li>[GitHub #6887] - Fixed a bug where changing the response language was not formatting correctly</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.2.2" date="2019-06-19"/>
    <release version="7.2.0" date="2019-06-12"/>
    <release version="7.1.1" date="2019-05-20"/>
    <release version="7.1.0" date="2019-05-14"/>
    <release version="7.0.9" date="2019-04-22"/>
    <release version="7.0.7" date="2019-03-29"/>
    <release version="7.0.6" date="2019-03-13"/>
    <release version="6.7.4" date="2019-02-26"/>
    <release version="6.7.3" date="2019-02-01"/>
    <release version="6.7.2" date="2019-01-22"/>
    <release version="6.7.1" date="2019-01-10"/>
    <release version="6.6.1" date="2018-12-11"/>
    <release version="6.5.3" date="2018-11-27"/>
    <release version="6.5.2" date="2018-11-07"/>
    <release version="6.4.4" date="2018-10-17"/>
    <release version="6.4.2" date="2018-10-08"/>
    <release version="6.3.0" date="2018-09-06"/>
    <release version="6.2.5" date="2018-08-20"/>
    <release version="6.2.4" date="2018-08-09"/>
    <release version="6.2.3" date="2018-08-02"/>
    <release version="6.2.2" date="2018-07-27"/>
    <release version="6.2.1" date="2018-07-25"/>
    <release version="6.1.4" date="2018-06-27"/>
    <release version="6.1.3" date="2018-05-25"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
